{
  "defaultAccounts": [
    { "email": "admin@foo.com", "password": "Always-There-50", "role": "ADMIN", "firstName": "Admin", "lastName": "Admin"
    },
    { "email": "medgroup@foo.com", "password": "Always-Ready-75", "role": "USER" , "firstName": "Med", "lastName": "Staff" }
  ],

  "defaultCategories": [
    { "category": "Readiness" },
    { "category": "Line of Duty" },
    { "category": "Profiles/Waivers" },
    { "category": "Medical Clearance" },
    { "category": "FLYERS" },
    { "category": "NON-FLYERS" },
    { "category": "Deployment" },
    { "category": "Occupational Health" },
    { "category": "Other" }
  ],

  "defaultQuestions": [
    {
      "category": "Readiness",
      "question": "Where do I find readiness information?",
      "answered": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Medical Clearance",
      "question": "What do I need for medical clearance?",
      "answered": false
    }
  ],

  "defaultFAQ": [
    {
      "category": "Readiness",
      "question": "How do I check my medical requirements?",
      "answer": "Access your IMR from the Air Force portal. https://asimsimr.health.mil/imr/myimr.aspx"
    },
    {
      "category": "Line of Duty",
      "question": "I’ve been hurt while on orders, what is the next step?",
      "answer": "If you were hurt during drill/AT orders get seen at Tripler ED on the day you were hurt. If you were hurt during AGR/MPA orders get seen at schedule an appointment with 15th MDG or go to Tripler ED for emergencies. Email 154MDG.GCC@us.af.mil for an LOD form only if you require follow-up care/surgery for an injury after your orders end date."
    },
    {
      "category": "Profiles/Waivers",
      "question": "How do I get a profile for duty/fitness restrictions?",
      "answer": "DSG: Please have your provider fill out a Request Medical Information (RMI) and submit to 154th MDG. (attach general RMI form) AGR/MPA: Schedule an appointment with your PCM at the 15th MDG."
    },
    {
      "category": "Medical Clearance",
      "question": "I’ve been selected for an AGR/MPA tour, how do I get medical clearance?",
      "answer": "Please ensure your IMR is GREEN. Send your AGR/MPA checklist to 154MDG.GCC@us.af.mil. Your unit should provide you with a checklist, medical does not provide a checklist. Medical clearance is an AF422 that we will create for you if you do not have one dated within 12 months."
    },
    {
      "category": "FLYERS",
      "question": "I am due for my FLY physical; how do I schedule an appointment?",
      "answer": "Complete your PHAQ on your MyIMR and then contact your Unit Health Monitor to schedule your appointment or you may call 808-789-0184 or email 154MDG.GCC@us.af.mil to schedule."
    },
    {
      "category": "FLYERS",
      "question": "How do I get a copy of my DD2992?",
      "answer": "Email 154MDG.GCC@us.af.mil for a copy."
    },
    {
      "category": "FLYERS",
      "question": "How often do I need to do my FLY physical?",
      "answer": "Every 12 months."
    },
    {
      "category": "FLYERS",
      "question": "How often do I need to do my dental?",
      "answer": "DSG: Every 12 months with your civilian dental and submit your DD Form 2813 to 154mdg.gcc@us.af.mil. AGR/MPA: Every 12 months with 15th Dental Clinic."
    },
    {
      "category": "NON-FLYERS",
      "question": "How do I schedule an appointment for something on my action list?",
      "answer": "Notify your Unit Health Monitor or email our org box 154mdg.gcc@us.af.mil."
    },
    {
      "category": "NON-FLYERS",
      "question": "How do I know what I am medically due for?",
      "answer": "Login to your MyIMR https://asimsimr.health.mil/imr/myimr.aspx."
    },
    {
      "category": "NON-FLYERS",
      "question": "How do I start my PHAQ?",
      "answer": "Login to your MyIMR https://asimsimr.health.mil/imr/myimr.aspx."
    },
    {
      "category": "NON-FLYERS",
      "question": "Why am I still showing due for PHA/MHA?",
      "answer": "You still need to complete your MHA (with QTC), once MHA is completed our providers will sign off during drill weekends. Email 154mdg.gcc@us.af.mil if needed for promotion/tour/deployment."
    },
    {
      "category": "Deployment",
      "question": "I’ve recently been tasked to deploy. How can I schedule an appointment to complete my medical requirements?",
      "answer": "Contact your UDM to coordinate an appointment with the Medical group."
    },
    {
      "category": "Occupational Health",
      "question": "How often do I update my shop roster as a supervisor?",
      "answer": "Quarterly (every 3 months)."
    },
    {
      "category": "Occupational Health",
      "question": "How often do I need to complete an audiogram?",
      "answer": "Annually."
    },
    {
      "category": "Occupational Health",
      "question": "Who do I contact if my audiogram is not updated in ASIMS?",
      "answer": "154th Public Health."
    },
    {
      "category": "Occupational Health",
      "question": "What happens if I fail my annual audiogram?",
      "answer": "You are required to complete a 14-hour noise free follow-up 1 audiogram the next day."
    },
    {
      "category": "Occupational Health",
      "question": "What happens if I fail My 14-hour noise free follow up 1 audiogram?",
      "answer": "You are required to complete a same day follow up 2 audiogram."
    },
    {
      "category": "Occupational Health",
      "question": "What happens when I Fail my same day follow-up 2 audiogram?",
      "answer": "You are required to complete a DD1753 form and a face-to-face ear exam with a provider to determine if you need an audiologist referral or re-established baseline."
    }
  ],

  "defaultPasscodes": [
    {
      "code": "1234",
      "createdAt": "2024-05-01T00:00:00Z",
      "expiredAt": "2024-12-31T23:59:59Z",
      "expired": false
    }
  ],

  "public": {
    "development": true
  }
}
